Nas Nakanishi, a nationally known comedian, and musician Miki Ka-chan invite wonderful guests and just play games for 30 minutes!
We will play all kinds of games from consumer keys to board games!
No way! Wait a minute! What are you going to do?
Nas Nakanishi's Game Kingdom
Thank you for watching!
We'll be back again this week.
Say something funny!
It's so scary!
Suddenly...
My nose came out.
It was so sudden, my nose came out.
We're back again this week with another episode of Game Kingdom.
Thank you very much!
And now, we have another wonderful guest this month!
Let me introduce them to you!
First of all, let's have a look at this gentleman.
Mirei Hoshina from Ellis Junior High School!
Mirei Hoshina!
There she is!
Hello.
I'm Mirei.
I'm Mirei Hoshina from Ellis Junior High School.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Here she is, the energetic girl from the popular idol group Eris.
She's a girl of the moment, a revolutionary girl of the moment.
If you're wondering about that, it's a little embarrassing.
I've never been introduced to her before.
I thought that's why I'm here today.
How about your game, Miru-chan?
I like competitive games like Bang Bang, but I'm really bad at them.
But I'm not very good at communicating with fans.
I do that.
I play a lot.
You're a Revolutionary Girl now, aren't you?
You're right. I'm right.
You just want to use it.You just want to use it!
You just want to use it!
And now, here he is for the second time!
Shinichi, the comedian to see you off!
Good morning.
Let's get on with the show.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
What happened when you suck at it?
Suddenly I sucked at it.
I believe you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I want it.
I should touch you more.
I don't know why I was so bad at it.
He's a superstar.
R1 champion.
How long can you hold your breath now?
You've changed.
No, Leon, you're the champion.
He's changed now, Leon!
Rion Tatsuhara.
Mr. Tajuhara.
I don't see him much.
He's a jerk.
He's got a heart of gold.
I'm looking forward to working with you all. Let's get to the game.
Let's get to the game.
Yachi Miki, please.
This month's game is this one.
In November, a new game
Momotetsu World is coming out in November.
I couldn't wait until then!
Momotaro Dentetsu Showa Heisei Zero Prevention is a classic!
Congratulations!
Let's face off for the first time in a year in the classic sugoroku game, Momotetsu!
Become the president of a railroad company and acquire properties all over the country as you aim to become the best in Japan in terms of the number of trains you've beaten!
The well-known King Bomby stands up as the strongest in the history of the series!The well-known King Bomby will stand up as the strongest in the history of the series!
We're looking forward to seeing you all, experienced players of Momotetsu, in a heated battle!
By the way, last time we did a three-week run, but we ran out of time, so we had to finish it in two years.
We had so much fun that this time we're going to make it through another three years.
Let's go!
Lady Peachtree!
What's with the pose? Poor Peach!
She's cute.
Cute but funny.
Once we've decided on our first destination, where is it?
Kyoto, Kyoto, Kyoto!
Mr. Osawa.
Yes, Lois.
You know Gifu?
Mr. Mikinami, Mr. President.
Let me get ahead of you.
Let's go.
I'm pretty sure I've had this card since the beginning.
Let's use it sparingly.
The "Blowout" card.
If there's a jump, does that mean they'll go somewhere else?
No, but there's a good chance we'll get close.
One, two, one. It'd be so cool to be the first one to do this.
That's so cool.
I'll do the talent.
I'm going to fly off the handle.
That's amazing.
Number 24.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Aaaaahhhhh!
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this in one shot?
Talent might do it.
You're a musician.
You've been duped.
All right, let's go.All right, let's go.
First one.
You better go for the first one.
You better go for the first one, 'cause you're gonna get it.
Come on, 12.
You know how to do that?
I know a way.
Please, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Hey...
You've got 100 million yen in your pocket to begin with! I'll give you 80 percent based on your face.
First time I've ever seen Colker's face. Glide, is that me?
I'll use it too.
I'll use it, too.
51, yes.
Wa five.
Hey.
I'll take it.
Whatever you want.
You know... you know... I want to go get my card.
I'll get used to it... but you'll get a card. What card?
What card? I've never seen that before!
Oh! When you're playing for the first time and you have a negative balance.
Someone will pay you for it!
Wow! That's so cool!
That's so sweet.
I don't want to finally go in against him.
We're off to a good start, except for President Mikiya.
Next May, everyone will be collecting cards, and the cards will come into play at the end of the month.
President Nasunaka, President Ogawa, we're almost to the finish line!
I'd love to get my first goal!
Let's spend it!
Let's use it. Let's buy him some money.
Please do.
Okay, Mikyan-chan.
Touch is good
Mr. Nagai, I'm here to show you.
Don't finish yet.Don't finish yet.
Five and six.
I'm gonna get there.
I'm gonna make it! I'm gonna make it! I'm gonna make it!
For the show.
I got it.
Too bad
It's too bad.
It's too close to call.
I can't go either way
I can't face either one because it's too close
People
What am I going to do with this face?
I wonder which face he's going to wear
It's the choice I don't want the most
It's a shame, but which face to choose?
The most difficult face
I had a face like this
It's so bad!
It's not heavy.
This is the worst!
But for Mina-chan's sake
Why are you going so far forward?
Don't go so far forward!
I'm glad there's a six.
There's a big six.
There's two, three and four, so be careful.
Okay, one.
This is a bad idea.
I'm going to replenish what Nasunakarinsan couldn't even do.
Because I'm going to do something that I've just done.
express
I see... you can do a hole-in-one.
You showed the R1 champion
Wait a minute...
Here we go.
I'll turn it on when I'm done.
Thirteen.13
I'm glad I did it.
Which face
Which face?
Hey, guys!
You suck at this!
Hey, camera!
Why are you on TV?
That place with the red light.
You can't stand in front of it.
That's funny.
What are you doing?
Your timing is terrible.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Don't be an idiot! If you make it in show business, I'm going to give you a big fat foot in the door!
Boss, see you off!
You're in full throttle right from the start.
President Hoshida
We're moving rapidly toward the goal.
World Kazu
Tokai
Aaaaaaah, boo-boo!
Thank you for your permission... please show us how cool Nakanishi is after you go home
He's so cool in summer!
All right!
Yes!
You've got a funny look on your face because a normal negative turned into money.
That's right.
Look at them... the guys are all black.
Which way is that?
Can you see them?
Oh, my God!
Wait, they're not coming this fast!
I wonder who the god of poverty will be?I'm curious to see who the god of poverty will be.
Here they come... here they come...
Oh, no!
Why?
Yay!
Oh, no!
Why me?
Pick one.
With other people.
Now choose a new destination
I'm easy to get to.
I see.
Come on.
Oh, shit.
Close, close, close.
Oh, man, that's not good.
But he can't get away?
Uh-oh.
There's an express gun.
You're not gonna give me anything?
What?
Turn it on.
Come on, come on, come on.
We'll be there soon.
For now.
The Railway Museum.
The Railway Museum Express
Oh, no.
It's slowing down.
Okay, go!
No, no, no...
But it'll stop right in Chichibu.
Put it on.
You can't.
We can't go over.
Once we get to Chichibu...Once you enter Chichibu...
There you go. There you go.
It would be nice to go to Chichibu
You can get a new car.
Chichibu
It's a long way to Hakodate, and it's a three-year race, so I'd like to keep the goal in mind... but lucky you.
I've got to go with that card... or I'll fly away... but... the moment Honda's helicopter goes up, that's the moment it gets exciting.
I don't know when it goes up. I don't know when it goes up.
It'll be on the monitor right in front of you.
Like this?
Just the helicopter?
All you viewers out there, you're going to be very, very excited.
Here we go!
The flying card!
Is the helicopter looking down?
It's going up!
It's coming to a stop!
It's stopping!
Hey!
How can it turn like that?
Oh, my God!
How can it spin like that?
You should do a comedy act once you have that theater.
Osaka Sales!
Yes!
Let's blow the old man away!
You should see this.
You want to do it?
If there's a chance of this happening...
We're going down.
Next up.
Let's say there's a chance of a jump.
I'll go.
Before Mr. Righty does.
What do you say, what do you say?
Okay.
Right, right, right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's it!
You're making a fool of yourself!
I see it!
Yokkaichi
Here, here, here!
Don't forget to send off the president, Ringo Ugami!
Oh, hell...
This is the worst!
This is hell!
I'm going to the loneliest song ever!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow!
Miyu-chan too!
Miiru-chan!
That means...
That's what it means.
Not "down" and "up".
Down... and up...
Down... up...
Down and up.
The lower part.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going!
I'm going to fly!
How's it going?
We're flying.
We're here now.
Jingle, jingle, jingle
Whoa, whoa, whoa
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
oh?
hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah.arrow with feathers that curve to the left (the first of two arrows to be fired)
arrow with feathers that curve to the left (the first of two arrows to be fired)
Wow.
Yeah.
That's a long way
How many times there
I won't finish 3 years by the time I reach the second destination
Oh, no.
I'm telling you, there's some serious butter in there.
All three failed to make it to the destination!
That's a big step in President Mikiya's favor.
Let's get some cards.
Just in time.
I see.
Now we can make them look like they're about to fly off the handle.
Face up.
Wow.
Now that's evolution.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
What is this?
C Result
Bomby in dimension
Bomby goes to another player
Oh no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He pulled everything!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's a scary face.
It's the face you made when Beaujolais Nouveau was first released.
No...
It's like this...
Oh...that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
eh? (used to get someone's attention)
It's like this.
Nice face
I'll be damned if I'm going to lift the ban on that.
The key point is how anyone other than President Mikiya will act from here on out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good, good, good.
You're in a much better position, Mr. Mikiya.
Card.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
But I need him to use up all his cards... the fast ones.
Now that's a major type!
Wow, seriously.
I'm serious.
That's really good.
That's a badass card.
You get all the money the others have.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Who's the rich guy?
President Natsunaka.
This is here, isn't it?
May I see something on that card you just gave me?
Yes, sir.
If you use it when the God of Poverty is around, he'll go play with the other presidents.
all the time.
The god of poverty is tiny.
He's not coming.
I'll go now.
Yes, sir.
What a surprise, Mr. President, to see you off!
President Mickey would like to score a goal and skip the conspiracy god to another president, but...
Misfortunes do follow unexpectedly, don't they?
You... thank you.Thank you very much.
You can fly to any station in any region you choose until you run out of cards, and it's great!
This card will be a key card.
Get as close as you can.
Maybe it's locked. Okay.
Lottery! Lottery cards!
Fourth prize. What's that?
What's fourth prize? Wow, that's huge!
What's that, fourth prize?
I'm scared, scared, scared. I want to be in trouble there.
Almost in the hole. Shikoku?
That's a coup de grace!
What's this? Why is it here?
Wow, that's nice.
Finally... the tide is turning for President Mikiya.
President Mikiya, I'd like to reach the finish line as soon as possible to lessen the damage from the god of poverty.
But first...
May I see the card again?
It's all about the money.
But that's money, isn't it?
But the new one...
He had 1.4 billion.
I see.
For the candy they gave us.
I've got two years.
No, no, no.
Who did you take it from?
What do you mean?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
It'll come out later. - Yes, of course it will.
I want it from the boss. Okay, from me.
I'll take it from me.
You scared me.
I got 1.4 billion from the boss.
That's great!
I got a little bit from the president.
Here you go.
What should we do? No, but let's go.What shall we do? No, but let's go.
Let's go ahead with the express train.
I really want to put Bee-Long Gum on the new one.
I want to give the new one a taste of hell.
I want the new one to taste hell.
I want the new one to taste hell. Why is that happening?
I'm out of money.
I took his credit card.
Please.
I can't just fly out to that property.
This is bad.
Right here.
We're getting away from it.
It's easy to get a ringer with someone else.
huh?
It's getting really scary.
Oh, man.
Look at his face. The look on his face when they lifted the ban on subs.
No, it's not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's too hard to unsubscribe.
I'll miss you.
I'm gonna miss you.
I could wait.
President Mikiya set foot in Hokkaido. I bought the property before I waited, but...
Oh, no way
It's so nice!
Oh, wait!
It's the Takakura lottery!
Oh no!
It's either the goal or the lottery!
Which one goes?
Even Bombay is on our side!
Amazing!
President Mikiya's unexpected assist from Bombee made it easier to score a goal.
Good luck!Good luck.
I'm only getting 1 or 2.
yes yes yes yes yes
Card Card
Angel card.
It's on Basil.
What's with the angel card?
I hope Mikyan gets the next one.
Oh, come on.
I'd like to win first prize, wouldn't you?
But that one...
Oh, come on...
Now.
Well...
What do you think?
The stage is hardly set up areas ера full of so much herauskan Bundesliga
Lining series peaches and other great adventures
President Ikike, just a few steps away from the goal
The one we'd forgotten about finally arrived!
Hey, hey, hey, now?
Here?
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's the little guy.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
We can't take the whole place.
Oh, shit.
This is a weird world.
This is bad.
We can't afford the lottery.
We can't afford to play the lottery.
I really don't.Really.
Come on, let's go.
This is hell.
I won't let it go down.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Watch out!
I'm never leaving this place.
Run, run, run!
They're crazy!
Go, go, go, go!
Run, run, run!
Okay, okay, okay.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let's see how far you can run.
I have no money.
Oh, no.
I'm going to send you off, Mr. President.
He's the next King Bomby.
Under the circumstances...
I'm going to take President Hoshina with me.
Minus...
But I'm willing to put up with that.
That's enough.
Are you okay?
Oh, no!
I've been fooled!
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
You're too good to be true, Mr. President.
Let's close the books.
Let's close the books!
Who will be the first place in total assets in the first year?
Oh, no!
Wow!Wow.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Thank you very much for the money you all gave us!
Well, folks, we're into our second year.
I'm sorry, I thought it was only two more years due to time constraints.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
It's over at this point.
I can't hold it any longer.
It's too much fun.
Yes, it is.
Why?
Because it's fun.
This will be our last year.
No way!
The third year is pretty turbulent.
I've never been to a third year of this show.
Three years at a time.
I won't do it!
I want to do 3 years!
I've wanted to do it for three years, too.
What?
What did you want to do?
Well, here we go... three years... now.
I don't want that.
It's two years of that.
I'm running out of time.
Wow, you're right, third year, I did have something I wanted to do.
You had something you wanted to do?
Yes, I did.
I'll ask you again.
I don't have time for this.
I don't have time.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
I'm sorry, Mr. Shinichi, but I don't think I'll be able to finish the second year at this rate.
Mikiya-chan, this part is very important.
Oh, yes.Oh, I see.
Ah, I see.
President Mikiya in a situation where only 1 or 2
If the body appears, it's the goal.
If 1 comes out, even King Mombee falls prey to an attack that will drive him to bankruptcy at once!
If it's a one! 2!
And that's all for this week. This month's ending theme is a present from Dublin.
Check it out!
Next week, the second half of the Peach Tennis Tournament!
I really, really, really saw Real Rombo.
That's why I bought it
The Real God of Poverty Shinichi Theater begins
I'm going to do all the bad things
He made me do a gag earlier.
So I didn't have any clothes on
There's one with flowers
There's a tree with flowers, too.
Somebody please bring this guy to heel.
Mysterious lyrics of the game Kingdom.
See you next week!
Comedy right straight next week too